let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "hazard", "answer": "Gefahr", "options": ["Gefahr", "anstrenged", "st\u00f6rend", "Rutsche"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "diversification", "answer": "Ver\u00e4nderungen", "options": ["Ver\u00e4nderungen", "Inhaltverzeichnis", "Gewerbschein", "zeitfresser"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "popularity", "answer": "Belibtheit", "options": ["Rauscht", "Belibtheit", "zeugnis", "schweringen"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "plant, enterprize", "answer": "Betrieb", "options": ["Selbverst\u00e4ndlich", "Rassen", "Tippschein", "Betrieb"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "lucky number", "answer": "Gl\u00fcckzahlen", "options": ["Gl\u00fcckzahlen", "zeugnis", "zettel", "so_gut_wie_gar"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "time eater", "answer": "zeitfresser", "options": ["zeitfresser", "externen", "\u00fcbringen", "Rauscht"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "original", "answer": "urspr\u00fcnglich", "options": ["urspr\u00fcnglich", "Ver\u00e4nderungen", "Gang", "zogen"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "replacer", "answer": "ersetzer", "options": ["Abschlusspr\u00fcfung", "dennoch", "Betrieb", "ersetzer"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "Civic, Citizen", "answer": "B\u00fcrger", "options": ["wohnwagen", "Gewerbschein", "B\u00fcrger", "Zusammengetragen"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "Public festival", "answer": "Volkfest", "options": ["Zusammengetragen", "gesamten", "Volkfest", "H\u00f6rst\u00f6rungen"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "hurry, urgent", "answer": "eillig", "options": ["eillig", "Volksport", "geregelten", "Hauptverkehrstra\u00dfe"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "Valueables", "answer": "wertsachen", "options": ["misserfolg", "unerheblich", "wertsachen", "zeitfresser"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "Rich values", "answer": "Reichwerte", "options": ["Rutsche", "empfindlichen", "Reichwerte", "Firmeninhaber"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "uses", "answer": "Verwendet", "options": ["kopfh\u00f6rer", "Verwendet", "Betreff", "begriff"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "stressful", "answer": "Belastend", "options": ["Zuschauer", "Belastend", "Zeitgeschehen", "Leistungen"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "thrilling", "answer": "spannende", "options": ["Lauffeuer", "spannende", "Tagesablauf", "sogar"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "Breakfast Table", "answer": "fr\u00fchst\u00fcckstich", "options": ["ersetzer", "Rutsche", "fr\u00fchst\u00fcckstich", "Schon_lange"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "back then", "answer": "damals", "options": ["geregelten", "festen", "Volksport", "damals"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "final exam", "answer": "Abschlusspr\u00fcfung", "options": ["Abschlusspr\u00fcfung", "Bewertungen", "L\u00e4rm", "Rasen"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "carpets, rugs", "answer": "Teppiche", "options": ["Teppiche", "Selbverst\u00e4ndlich", "waisenkind", "Zusammengetragen"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "front door", "answer": "Haust\u00fcr", "options": ["Rasen", "Berufswahl", "Haust\u00fcr", "damals"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "whisper, pisumatu", "answer": "Rauscht", "options": ["Rauscht", "Rutsche", "schallschutzfenster", "fr\u00fchst\u00fcckstich"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "deep", "answer": "Tiefe", "options": ["Tiefe", "Firmeninhaber", "geregelten", "Niveau"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Heart attack", "answer": "Herzinfarkt", "options": ["Rasen", "Betrieb", "Herzinfarkt", "Gl\u00fcckzahlen"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "Passage, \u0cae\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0c97", "answer": "Gang", "options": ["genauso", "Gang", "misserfolg", "\u00fcbrig"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "even, yet", "answer": "sogar", "options": ["sogar", "L\u00e4rmbelastigung", "wertsachen", "wohnsitz"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "alaram clock ring", "answer": "weckerlingeln", "options": ["\u00dcberschrift", "weckerlingeln", "Umst\u00e4ndlich", "Reichwerte"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "coming school", "answer": "stammschule", "options": ["Lautst\u00e4rke", "Beschwerden", "stammschule", "schausteller"]}, {"numb": 29, "question": "wild fire", "answer": "Lauffeuer", "options": ["Lauffeuer", "los", "anstrenged", "zogen"]}, {"numb": 30, "question": "failure", "answer": "misserfolg", "options": ["misserfolg", "dauerhaft", "gesamten", "stammschule"]}, {"numb": 31, "question": "sound proof windows", "answer": "schallschutzfenster", "options": ["Tippschein", "misserfolg", "schallschutzfenster", "stammschule"]}, {"numb": 32, "question": "trade certificate", "answer": "Gewerbschein", "options": ["wohnwagen", "zeugnis", "Verkehrsl\u00e4rm", "Gewerbschein"]}, {"numb": 33, "question": "Races,\u0c9c\u0ca8\u0cbe\u0ce6\u0c97 (not fast speed race)", "answer": "Rasen", "options": ["staatkassen", "Berufswahl", "Rasen", "geregelten"]}, {"numb": 34, "question": "Valuation", "answer": "Bewertungen", "options": ["stammschule", "Gl\u00fcckzahlen", "Bewertungen", "Aktuell"]}, {"numb": 35, "question": "hours long", "answer": "stundenlang", "options": ["Reichwerte", "stundenlang", "staatkassen", "Tagesablauf"]}, {"numb": 36, "question": "Home page", "answer": "Startseite", "options": ["Herzinfarkt", "Gel\u00e4nder", "Umst\u00e4ndlich", "Startseite"]}, {"numb": 37, "question": "constantly, always", "answer": "st\u00e4ndig", "options": ["Verkehrsl\u00e4rm", "st\u00e4ndig", "eben", "fr\u00fchst\u00fcckstich"]}, {"numb": 38, "question": "just like that", "answer": "genauso", "options": ["Aktuell", "Ver\u00e4nderungen", "Schon_lange", "genauso"]}, {"numb": 39, "question": "Unsettled life", "answer": "wanderleben", "options": ["\u00fcbrig", "wanderleben", "Lauffeuer", "Bewertungen"]}, {"numb": 40, "question": "disturbing", "answer": "st\u00f6rend", "options": ["oberfl\u00e4chlich", "st\u00f6rend", "ersetzer", "Nachtruhe"]}, {"numb": 41, "question": "Night peace", "answer": "Nachtruhe", "options": ["schweringen", "Nachtruhe", "Zusammengetragen", "stundenlang"]}, {"numb": 42, "question": "exotic", "answer": "exotisch", "options": ["\u00dcberschrift", "exotisch", "Betrieb", "Tippschein"]}, {"numb": 43, "question": "certificate,report", "answer": "zeugnis", "options": ["fr\u00fchst\u00fcckstich", "zeugnis", "Niveau", "gesamten"]}, {"numb": 44, "question": "Orphan", "answer": "waisenkind", "options": ["vertra\u00fcnw\u00fcrdig", "wanderleben", "waisenkind", "Nachtruhe"]}, {"numb": 45, "question": "extensive,substantial, \u0c97\u0ca3\u0ca8\u0cc0\u0caf, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0caa\u0c95\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf", "answer": "ausgiebig", "options": ["wohl", "Berufswahl", "Verkehrsl\u00e4rm", "ausgiebig"]}, {"numb": 46, "question": "receipt, revenue", "answer": "Einnahmen", "options": ["kopfh\u00f6rer", "Einnahmen", "irgendwann", "stammschule"]}, {"numb": 47, "question": "slide", "answer": "Rutsche", "options": ["Zusammengetragen", "eben", "kopfh\u00f6rer", "Rutsche"]}, {"numb": 48, "question": "almost", "answer": "herum", "options": ["begriff", "genauso", "herum", "L\u00e4rmbelastigung"]}, {"numb": 49, "question": "governed", "answer": "geregelten", "options": ["begriff", "geregelten", "Rutsche", "Tippschein"]}, {"numb": 50, "question": "hearing nerve", "answer": "H\u00f6rnerven", "options": ["festen", "zugang", "H\u00f6rnerven", "Mitglieder"]}, {"numb": 51, "question": "heart disorder", "answer": "H\u00f6rst\u00f6rungen", "options": ["Firmeninhaber", "gewinnbringende", "berufst\u00e4tig", "H\u00f6rst\u00f6rungen"]}, {"numb": 52, "question": "expression", "answer": "\u00c4u\u00dferungen", "options": ["\u00c4u\u00dferungen", "Stressausl\u00f6sen", "exotisch", "Wohlbefinden"]}, {"numb": 53, "question": "Resposibility", "answer": "verantwortung", "options": ["gewinnbringende", "verantwortung", "wertsachen", "Gefahr"]}, {"numb": 54, "question": "Race, speed race", "answer": "Rassen", "options": ["Aktuell", "eillig", "Rassen", "externen"]}, {"numb": 55, "question": "Current", "answer": "Aktuell", "options": ["Rutsche", "geregelten", "Aktuell", "Haust\u00fcr"]}, {"numb": 56, "question": "well being", "answer": "Wohlbefinden", "options": ["Selbverst\u00e4ndlich", "Wohlbefinden", "oberfl\u00e4chlich", "Rassen"]}, {"numb": 57, "question": "transmissions", "answer": "\u00fcbertragungen", "options": ["Lauffeuer", "\u00fcbertragungen", "Rauscht", "Zuschauer"]}, {"numb": 58, "question": "overall", "answer": "gesamten", "options": ["gesamten", "Reichwerte", "geregelten", "Berufswahl"]}, {"numb": 59, "question": "daily routine", "answer": "Tagesablauf", "options": ["Rauscht", "Tagesablauf", "schallschutzfenster", "Lautst\u00e4rke"]}, {"numb": 60, "question": "fate,destiny", "answer": "los", "options": ["oberfl\u00e4chlich", "los", "Ver\u00e4nderungen", "\u00dcberschrift"]}, {"numb": 61, "question": "Access", "answer": "zugang", "options": ["zugang", "Gewerbschein", "Abreise", "eingebu\u00dft"]}, {"numb": 62, "question": "noise pollution", "answer": "L\u00e4rmveraursacher", "options": ["L\u00e4rmveraursacher", "irgendwann", "eingebu\u00dft", "Haust\u00fcr"]}, {"numb": 63, "question": "pullen", "answer": "zogen", "options": ["Bahnfahten", "schallschutzfenster", "zogen", "Umst\u00e4ndlich"]}, {"numb": 64, "question": "Media Day", "answer": "Medientag", "options": ["Medientag", "\u00dcberall", "Volkfestplatz", "m\u00f6glicherweise"]}, {"numb": 65, "question": "irrelevant \u0c85\u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb8\u0ccd\u0ca4\u0cc1\u0ca4", "answer": "unerheblich", "options": ["unerheblich", "externen", "feststehen", "festen"]}, {"numb": 66, "question": "national sport", "answer": "Volksport", "options": ["Volksport", "kopfh\u00f6rer", "st\u00f6rend", "fr\u00fchst\u00fcckstich"]}, {"numb": 67, "question": "tiring,exhausting", "answer": "anstrenged", "options": ["zeitfresser", "sensibler", "anstrenged", "Tippschein"]}, {"numb": 68, "question": "exceptionally", "answer": "ausnahmeweise", "options": ["genauso", "Zeitgeschehen", "ausnahmeweise", "Aktuell"]}, {"numb": 69, "question": "heading", "answer": "\u00dcberschrift", "options": ["waisenkind", "so_gut_wie_gar", "feststehen", "\u00dcberschrift"]}, {"numb": 70, "question": "Carried together", "answer": "Zusammengetragen", "options": ["staatkassen", "wohnwagen", "Tippschein", "Zusammengetragen"]}, {"numb": 71, "question": "News portals", "answer": "Nachrichtsportale", "options": ["Lautst\u00e4rke", "Nachrichtsportale", "misserfolg", "Rassen"]}, {"numb": 72, "question": "mainly", "answer": "haupts\u00e4chlich", "options": ["Volkfest", "empfindlichen", "haupts\u00e4chlich", "Gewerbschein"]}, {"numb": 73, "question": "more sensitive", "answer": "sensibler", "options": ["sensibler", "geregelten", "Rauscht", "Bahnfahten"]}, {"numb": 74, "question": "Subject, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0cb7\u0caf", "answer": "Betreff", "options": ["sensibler", "gewinnbringende", "stammschule", "Betreff"]}, {"numb": 75, "question": "slip, note, bill, \u0c9a\u0cc0\u0c9f\u0cbf", "answer": "zettel", "options": ["damals", "zettel", "so_gut_wie_gar", "\u00dcberschrift"]}, {"numb": 76, "question": "to be fixed", "answer": "feststehen", "options": ["Verkehrsl\u00e4rm", "misserfolg", "feststehen", "Berufswahl"]}, {"numb": 77, "question": "achievements", "answer": "Leistungen", "options": ["Leistungen", "H\u00f6rst\u00f6rungen", "Gewerbschein", "wohnsitz"]}, {"numb": 78, "question": "slight, minor", "answer": "gering", "options": ["gering", "gesamten", "Zeitgeschehen", "genauso"]}, {"numb": 79, "question": "durable, permanent", "answer": "dauerhaft", "options": ["wertsachen", "ausnahmeweise", "dauerhaft", "grunds\u00e4tzlich"]}, {"numb": 80, "question": "spectator", "answer": "Zuschauer", "options": ["dennoch", "gesamten", "zeugnis", "Zuschauer"]}, {"numb": 81, "question": "volume, loudness", "answer": "Lautst\u00e4rke", "options": ["Ver\u00e4nderungen", "grunds\u00e4tzlich", "Lautst\u00e4rke", "waisenkind"]}, {"numb": 82, "question": "possibly", "answer": "m\u00f6glicherweise", "options": ["so_gut_wie_gar", "gewinnbringende", "m\u00f6glicherweise", "empfindlichen"]}, {"numb": 83, "question": "lottery ticket", "answer": "Tippschein", "options": ["gering", "schweringen", "Tippschein", "B\u00fcrger"]}, {"numb": 84, "question": "long time", "answer": "Schon_lange", "options": ["Inhaltverzeichnis", "Schon_lange", "Tiefe", "Teppiche"]}, {"numb": 85, "question": "thunder", "answer": "donnert", "options": ["Wohlbefinden", "Leistungen", "donnert", "irgendwann"]}, {"numb": 86, "question": "self evident", "answer": "Selbverst\u00e4ndlich", "options": ["Selbverst\u00e4ndlich", "wertsachen", "begriff", "\u00c4u\u00dferungen"]}, {"numb": 87, "question": "train rides", "answer": "Bahnfahten", "options": ["Bahnfahten", "haupts\u00e4chlich", "Rutsche", "H\u00f6rst\u00f6rungen"]}, {"numb": 88, "question": "van, Caravan", "answer": "wohnwagen", "options": ["fr\u00fchst\u00fcckstich", "schausteller", "wohnwagen", "oberfl\u00e4chlich"]}, {"numb": 89, "question": "triangle", "answer": "Dreieck", "options": ["Wohlbefinden", "Berghof", "Haust\u00fcr", "Dreieck"]}, {"numb": 90, "question": "level", "answer": "Niveau", "options": ["zogen", "Zuschauer", "Niveau", "festen"]}, {"numb": 91, "question": "members", "answer": "Mitglieder", "options": ["Mitglieder", "\u00dcberschrift", "urspr\u00fcnglich", "spannende"]}, {"numb": 92, "question": "yet,still", "answer": "dennoch", "options": ["Belastend", "zeitfresser", "dennoch", "gering"]}, {"numb": 93, "question": "current affairs, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0c9a\u0cb2\u0cbf\u0ca4 \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0ca6\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cae\u0cbe\u0ca8", "answer": "Zeitgeschehen", "options": ["\u00dcberall", "Volkfest", "Zeitgeschehen", "gering"]}, {"numb": 94, "question": "almost not at all", "answer": "so_gut_wie_gar", "options": ["eillig", "oberfl\u00e4chlich", "L\u00e4rmveraursacher", "so_gut_wie_gar"]}, {"numb": 95, "question": "all the rest", "answer": "\u00fcbringen", "options": ["staatkassen", "los", "\u00fcbringen", "schausteller"]}, {"numb": 96, "question": "sensitive", "answer": "empfindlichen", "options": ["empfindlichen", "Selbverst\u00e4ndlich", "zettel", "Stressausl\u00f6sen"]}, {"numb": 97, "question": "rare", "answer": "selten", "options": ["spannende", "Startseite", "selten", "sensibler"]}, {"numb": 98, "question": "even", "answer": "eben", "options": ["Volksport", "\u00fcbertragungen", "wohnwagen", "eben"]}, {"numb": 99, "question": "superficial, \u0cac\u0cbe\u0cb9\u0ccd\u0caf, \u0cb9\u0cc1\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0cb2\u0ccd\u0cb2\u0ca6", "answer": "oberfl\u00e4chlich", "options": ["oberfl\u00e4chlich", "empfindlichen", "Schon_lange", "Zeitgeschehen"]}, {"numb": 100, "question": "carrier choice", "answer": "Berufswahl", "options": ["sogar", "Lauffeuer", "Verkehrsl\u00e4rm", "Berufswahl"]}, {"numb": 101, "question": "fairplace", "answer": "Volkfestplatz", "options": ["misserfolg", "verantwortung", "Volkfestplatz", "sensibler"]}, {"numb": 102, "question": "city treasuries", "answer": "staatkassen", "options": ["staatkassen", "Tippschein", "so_gut_wie_gar", "L\u00e4rm"]}, {"numb": 103, "question": "everywhere", "answer": "\u00dcberall", "options": ["Dreieck", "gering", "spannende", "\u00dcberall"]}, {"numb": 104, "question": "Noise", "answer": "ger\u00e4usche", "options": ["wanderleben", "ger\u00e4usche", "\u00dcberall", "selten"]}, {"numb": 105, "question": "residence", "answer": "wohnsitz", "options": ["genauso", "staatkassen", "wohnsitz", "Leistungen"]}, {"numb": 106, "question": "noise pollution", "answer": "L\u00e4rmbelastigung", "options": ["L\u00e4rmbelastigung", "Startseite", "Inhaltverzeichnis", "misserfolg"]}, {"numb": 107, "question": "stress triggers", "answer": "Stressausl\u00f6sen", "options": ["Rauscht", "Betreff", "Stressausl\u00f6sen", "selten"]}, {"numb": 108, "question": "Contents", "answer": "Inhaltverzeichnis", "options": ["Betrieb", "Rutsche", "Ver\u00e4nderungen", "Inhaltverzeichnis"]}, {"numb": 109, "question": "laborious, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0caf\u0cbe\u0cb8\u0c95\u0cb0", "answer": "Umst\u00e4ndlich", "options": ["kopfh\u00f6rer", "Zuschauer", "Umst\u00e4ndlich", "zogen"]}, {"numb": 110, "question": "trustworthy", "answer": "vertra\u00fcnw\u00fcrdig", "options": ["Haust\u00fcr", "Gefahr", "vertra\u00fcnw\u00fcrdig", "gewinnbringende"]}, {"numb": 111, "question": "term", "answer": "begriff", "options": ["begriff", "dauerhaft", "Einnahmen", "\u00fcbrig"]}, {"numb": 112, "question": "complaints", "answer": "Beschwerden", "options": ["geregelten", "Einnahmen", "Beschwerden", "kopfh\u00f6rer"]}, {"numb": 113, "question": "Profittable", "answer": "gewinnbringende", "options": ["Volkfestplatz", "Volksport", "wanderleben", "gewinnbringende"]}, {"numb": 114, "question": "suffered", "answer": "eingebu\u00dft", "options": ["Einnahmen", "eingebu\u00dft", "Belastend", "L\u00e4rm"]}, {"numb": 115, "question": "headphone", "answer": "kopfh\u00f6rer", "options": ["empfindlichen", "Abreise", "kopfh\u00f6rer", "Verwendet"]}, {"numb": 116, "question": "Spiritual, \u0c86\u0ca7\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cae\u0cbf\u0c95", "answer": "seelisches", "options": ["fr\u00fchst\u00fcckstich", "L\u00e4rm", "Volkfestplatz", "seelisches"]}, {"numb": 117, "question": "company owner", "answer": "Firmeninhaber", "options": ["Medientag", "Firmeninhaber", "Rasen", "Belibtheit"]}, {"numb": 118, "question": "showman", "answer": "schausteller", "options": ["Startseite", "schausteller", "Betreff", "Verwendet"]}, {"numb": 119, "question": "railing", "answer": "Gel\u00e4nder", "options": ["zogen", "Verkehrsl\u00e4rm", "Gel\u00e4nder", "Zusammengetragen"]}, {"numb": 120, "question": "more difficulty", "answer": "schweringen", "options": ["Rassen", "Nachrichtsportale", "Berghof", "schweringen"]}, {"numb": 121, "question": "traffic noise", "answer": "Verkehrsl\u00e4rm", "options": ["L\u00e4rmveraursacher", "zeitfresser", "Verkehrsl\u00e4rm", "empfindlichen"]}, {"numb": 122, "question": "professional, working", "answer": "berufst\u00e4tig", "options": ["stammschule", "berufst\u00e4tig", "gesamten", "wohnsitz"]}, {"numb": 123, "question": "external", "answer": "externen", "options": ["externen", "Wohlbefinden", "\u00c4u\u00dferungen", "zeugnis"]}, {"numb": 124, "question": "main road", "answer": "Hauptverkehrstra\u00dfe", "options": ["Hauptverkehrstra\u00dfe", "\u00dcberall", "L\u00e4rmbelastigung", "Medientag"]}, {"numb": 125, "question": "Departure", "answer": "Abreise", "options": ["irgendwann", "Abreise", "wohnwagen", "sensibler"]}, {"numb": 126, "question": "house rules", "answer": "Hausordnung", "options": ["\u00fcbrig", "zugang", "L\u00e4rmveraursacher", "Hausordnung"]}, {"numb": 127, "question": "strong hold", "answer": "festen", "options": ["herum", "Verwendet", "festen", "Leistungen"]}, {"numb": 128, "question": "time", "answer": "zeiten", "options": ["spannende", "begriff", "zeiten", "Firmeninhaber"]}, {"numb": 129, "question": "ward", "answer": "Berghof", "options": ["Inhaltverzeichnis", "Rauscht", "Berghof", "dauerhaft"]}, {"numb": 130, "question": "Noise", "answer": "L\u00e4rm", "options": ["Betreff", "\u00fcbrig", "L\u00e4rm", "H\u00f6rst\u00f6rungen"]}, {"numb": 131, "question": "well", "answer": "wohl", "options": ["st\u00f6rend", "wohl", "Selbverst\u00e4ndlich", "los"]}, {"numb": 132, "question": "basically", "answer": "grunds\u00e4tzlich", "options": ["grunds\u00e4tzlich", "\u00fcbertragungen", "empfindlichen", "L\u00e4rmbelastigung"]}, {"numb": 133, "question": "somewhere", "answer": "irgendwann", "options": ["ersetzer", "irgendwann", "Gel\u00e4nder", "staatkassen"]}, {"numb": 134, "question": "remaning, \u0c89\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0ca6", "answer": "\u00fcbrig", "options": ["Abreise", "wohnsitz", "Bahnfahten", "\u00fcbrig"]}];